Guide to the Peter Reddaway Samizdat collection, 1950-2010 GRC0002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Mainstream, Circa 1960s to 1990s; Series 4
  - Individual, Series 4 Subseries 4
    - Kovalyovs [Ivan] Osipova [Tatiana] [4/5], 1979-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Kovalyovs [Ivan] Osipova [Tatiana] [5/5], 1976-1979; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - [Koverko, Elena], 1983 July 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - [Kozhevnikov, Yevgenny], 1978 October 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - [Kozlova, Elena], 1980 April 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - [Kozlovskii, Evgeny], 1981 December 12-1983 May 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - [Krainik, Mikola], 1980 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - [Krakhmal'nikova, Zoia], 1982 April 8-1987 October 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - [Krasivski, Zinovii], 1973-1978 August 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - [Krasnovskaia, Zoia], 1977 July 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - [Krasovskii, O.], 1978 September 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - [Kravchuk, Mikhail], 1979 May 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - [Kristallova, Liudmila], 1980 February 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - [Kristi, Irina], 1973 December 4-1985 May 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - [Kritskii, Eduard], 1983-1984; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - [Kriuchkov, Nikolai], 1985 April 13-1988 October 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - [Kriukov, V. N.], 1968 April 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - [Kriutshkow, Nikolai], 1985 April 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - [Kronidov, A.], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - [Krylsky, Jan], 1973 September 4-1980 February 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - [Kucherenko, Varvara], 1978 February 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - [Kudirka, Simas], 1971 August 7-1971 September 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - [Kudrin, Viktor], 1976 August 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - [Kukaredzhi, Lev], 1987 July 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - [Kukk, Iurii], 1979 April 10-1981 May 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - [Kukobaka, Mikhail], 1976 December 2-1983 October 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - [Kuleshov, Eduard], 1978 December 14-1981 November 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - [Kuma, Teovils], 1984 April 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - [Kurdiani, Svetlana], 1985 June 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - [Kurginian, S. M.], 1980 July 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - [Kurnosov, Valerii], 1980 December 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - [Kushev, Evgenii], 1974 February 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - [Kutiavin, Aleksandr Zennady], 1989 March 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - [Kutik, Vadim], 1988 January 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - [Kuvakin, Vsevolod], 1976 October 20-1983 May 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - [Kuzenkov, Anatoly], 1974 March 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - [Kuzkin, Aleksandr], 1982 May 24-1982 September 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - [Kuznetsov, Aleksei], 1984 February 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - [Kuznetsov, Eduard], 1976-1981 February 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - [Kuznetsov, Gennady], 1976 July 4-1982 March 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - [Kuznetsov, Liudmila], 1979 April 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - [Kuznetsov, Sergei], 1987 October 9-1989 December 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - [Kuznetsov, Viktor], 1966 December 15-1971 January 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - [Kvachevskii, Orion], 1968 February 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - [Kvetsko, Dmitrii], 1977 December 10-1979 January 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - [Ladov, L.], 1972 July-1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - [Lamport, Bernard], 1985 April 13-1985 April 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - M[al'va] Landa [1/2], 1972-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Landa, M[al'va] [2/2], 1976-1987; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - [Lapienis, Vladas], 1985 February 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - [Lapik, Filipp], 1977-1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - [Lapin, Vladimir], 1970 December 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - [Lapmann, Johannes], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - [Lashkova, Vera], 1978 July 6-1983 May 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - [Laskin, Vladimir], 1976 May 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - [Laturnus, Gelmund], 1979 May 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - [Laurova, Inna], 1982 January 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - [Lavra (Monastery)], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - [Lavut, Alexandr], 1980 November 14-1981 May 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - [Lazareva, Natalya], 1982 July 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - [Lazda, Peteris], 1990 December 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - [Lazuta, Ivan], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - [Lebedeva, Tat'iana], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Leikina [Meita], 1975 September 3-1976 December 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - [Lein, Aleksandra], 1984 February 21-1984 February 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - [Lein, Evgenii], 1981 May 13-1981 August 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - [Leivand, Jaak], 1980 January 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - [Leonidov, Mikhail], 1988 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - [Leonov, Dmitrii], 1988 November 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - [Lepilina, Svetlana], 1981 February 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - [Lerner, Aleksandr], 1975 September 13-1987 February 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - [Lert, Raisa], 1977 January 23-1980 June 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - [Lesnik, Evgeniia], 1985 March 1-1985 March 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - [Letter, anonymous, April 1973], 1973 April; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - [Levich, Benjamin], 1973 August 17-1978 December 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - [Levin, Sonia], 1981 July 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Levitin [(-Krasnov), Anatoly], 1971 January 26-1987 April 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - [Lezov, Sergei], 1988 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - [Liadov, L.], 1972 February 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - [Liakhov, Aleksandr], 1977 May 25-1977 June 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - [Liapin, Aleksander], 1978 April 22-1981 April 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - [Lifshits, Chara], 1979-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - [Linitsky, Vitaly], 1981 March 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - [Lipinskaya, Vera], 1982 November 24-1984 January 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - [Lipkin, Semen], 1979; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - [Lishchenko, Oleg], 1990 June 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - [Lisov, Vasilii], 1976 March-1979 November 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - [Listov, Iurii], 1987 July 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - [Litvin, Yuri], 1982 November 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - [Litvinov, Pavel], 1968 January 21-1974 November 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - [Liubarskii, Kronid], 1972 October 30-1980 February; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - [Liubich, Tatiana], 1986 March 14-1986 March 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - [Lokshin, Osip], 1982 January 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - [Lorentsson, Aleksei], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - [Los' Tamara], 1979 February 2-1979 June 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - [Lozansky, Eward Tatyana], 1979 February 14-1982 December 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - [Lubman, A.], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - [Lubman, Leonid], 1978 April 11-1987 November 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - [Lukash, Valerii], 1985 December 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - [Luk'ianov, Erman], 1982 February 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - [Lukyanenko, Lev], 1961 May 20-1979 January 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - [Lunin, M.], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - [Lupinos, Anatolii], 1980 June 26-1981 August 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - [Lutsyk, Mykhalo], 1979 February 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - [Lytkin, Ivan], 1977 November 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - [Lyubimov, Yuri], 1987 January 6-1988 February 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - [Mad'iar, P. I.], 1987 October 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - [Madisson, Tiit], 1981 May 17-1982 November 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - [Magala, Valerii], 1989 January 8-1990 January 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - [Magarik, Aleksei], 1987 January 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - [Magarik, Anna], 1981 December 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - [Magarik, V. A.], 1981 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - [Magidovich, Aleksandr'], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - [Mailanov, Vazif], 1975?-1987 July 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - [Makarenko, Mikhail], 1976 May 1-2007 March 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - [Makar-Limenova, Leonid], 1981 January 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - [Makeeva, Valeriia], 1979 April 14-1979 November 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - [Maksimov, Aleksandr' Galina], 1980 February 17-1980 April 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - [Maksimov, Iurii], 1979 March 14-1982 December 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - [Maksimov, Vladimir], 1973 May 15-1973 November 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - [Malachkin, Aleksandr], 1987 May 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - [Malafeev, V. S.], 1980 February 20-1980 March 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - [Malakhovskaia, Natalia], 1979 November-1980 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - [Maliarevskii, A. P.], 1979 September 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - [Maliarevskii, Sergei], 1979 March; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - [Malinkovich, Vladimir], 1979 March 8-1979 August 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - [Malkazian, Aleksandr'], 1976 December 5-1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - [Malozhenskii, Vasil'], 1975 December 8-1976 April 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - [Mamonova, Tat'iana], 1979 November 20-1981 March 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - [Manchur, Stepan], 1977 May 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - [Mandel'shtam, Nadezhda], 1971 December 10-1981 February 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Maramzin [Vladimir] + Kheifets [Mikhail], 1969-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Marchenko [Anatoly Valerii] [1/2], 1974 January 18-1986 December 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Marchenko [Anatoly Valerii] [1/2], 1968 September 13-1986 December 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - [Marchuk, Artur], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - [Markin, Evgenii], 1972 January 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - [Markman, Vladimir], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - [Markosian, Razmik], 1971 July 21-1977 March 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - [Markov, Dmitrii], 1984 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - [Markus, Sergei], 1984 May 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - [Marsal, Artur], 1981 February 18-1982 January 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - [Martynov, Evgennii], 1978 July 18-1978 December 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Martynov, Grigori, 1983 July 18-1989 March; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - [Martynov, Ivan], 1982 February 20-1984 January 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - [Martyrosan, Martin], 1982 January 23-1982 February 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - [Maryasin, Aleksandr], 1980 June 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - [Mashkov, Iurii], 1978 February 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - [Mashkova, Valentina], 1974 June 7-1974 June 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - [Massover, Iurii] [1/2], 1990 March 6-1990 June 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Massover [Yuri] [2/2], 1989-1992 June 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - [Matik, Kalju], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - [Matiulionis, Jonas-Kastytis], 1985 February 13-1985 October 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - [Matusevich, Mikola], 1980 December 12-1981 January 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - [Matveev, Ia.], 1973; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - [Matviiuk, Kuz'ma], 1978 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - [Mavromati, Oleg], 1988 November 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - [Mazur, Dmitrii], 1980 December 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - [Mazurov, Vladimir], 1986 June 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - [Mednikov, Vladimir Nina], 1980 September 16-1983 August 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - [Medushevskaia, Tatiana], 1978 March 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - [Medvedev, Pavel], 1990 August 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Medvedev, Roy, 1970-1987; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - R[oy] + Zh[ores] Medvedev [1/5], 1966-1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - R[oy] + Zh[ores] Medvedev [2/5], 1969-1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - R[oy] + Zh[ores] Medvedev [3/5], 1971-1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - R[oy] + Zh[ores] Medvedev [4/5], 1971-1974; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - R[oy] + Zh[ores] Medvedev [5/5], 1972-1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Medvedev, Zhores, 1978-1982; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - [Medvedkov, Iurii Ol'ga], 1982 December 17-1986 June 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - [Meilakh, Mikhail], 1986 August 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - [Meiman, Naum], 1975 August 5-1981 October 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - [Melamed, Vladimir], 1982 January 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - [Melchuk, Igor'], 1976 January 27-1977 February 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - [Mel'nik, Mikhail], 1972 July 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - [Men, Aleksandr], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - [Mendelevich, Joseph], 1979 June 13-1980 October 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - [Merenkov, Sergei Stanislavovich], 1987 November 17-1992 September 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - [Merkushev, Viachislav], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - [Meshener, Iosif], 1975 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - [Meshko, Oksana], 1978 November 8-1982; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - [Miasnikov, Aleksei], 1981 January 30-1988 July 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - [Mikhailev, Aleksandr], 1975 August 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - [Mikhailov], 1974 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - [Mikhailov, Boris], 1974 January 23-1983 October 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - [Mikhailov, Georgii], 1986 March 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Mikhailov, G[regory] [1/3], 1968; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Mikhailov, G[regory] [2/3], 1982-1986; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Mikhailov, G[regory] [3/3], 1974-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - [Mikhailov, V.V.], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - [Mikheev, Dmitrii], 1979 September 20-1981 July; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - [Mikhel', Nina], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - [Mikitko, Ia.], 1976 May 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - [Milgrom-Sharanskii, Ida], 1977 May 13-1979 February 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - [Miliakova, Tamara], 1987 January 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - [Miliutin, Oleg], 1980 January 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - [Miller, Genrikh], 1981 September 15-1981 October 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - [Miller, Georgii Boris], 1983; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - [Miniakov, Dmitri], 1981 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - [Mironov, Aleksandr], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - [Miroshnik, Vladimir], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - [Mitiashin, Boris], 1977 May 14-1985 February 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - [Mitiunov, Iurii], 1986 April 9-1987 November 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - [Miulberg, Adol'f], 1970 July; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - [Mkrtchian, Ishkhan], 1981 December 25-1985 June 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - [Mniukh, Iurii], 1977 February 7-1977 November 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - [Moiceenko, Tamara], 1987 March 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - [Moiceeva, Elena], 1985 February 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - [Mokoviichuk, Grigorii], 1979; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - [Mokrov, Evgenii], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - [Moloshenskii, Vasilii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - [Molostvov, Mikhail], 1982; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - [Monastyrskii, Boris], 1976 May 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - [Monblanov, Viktor], 1979 March-1982 June 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - [Moreev, Ivan], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Moroz, V[alentin], 1972 January 28-1979 September 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Moroz [Valentyn], 1974-1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - [Morozov, Mark], 1977 August 5-1984 March 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - [Morozov, Valerian], 1989 March 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Morozov, Vichieslav, 1979-1989; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - [Morozov, Vladimir], 1979 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - [Mostovoi, Vacilii], 1976-1988 March 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - [Mouzika, Vladimir], 1983 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - [Muchkin, Vitalii], 1986 July 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - [Mukhametshin, Boris], 1977 March 29-1979 October 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - [Murakhas, Nurfet], 1983 May 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - [Muralov, Nikolai], 1987 July 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - [Muratov, Nikolai], 1987 July 18-1988 December 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - [Murazhenko, Aleksei], 1977 December 17-1982 February 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - [Musatov, Georgii], 1976 September 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - [Mustafaeva, Adzhimelek Afife], 1976 December 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - [Naboka, Sergei], 1981 May-1981 October; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - [Nagapetian, Shagen], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - [Nagle, Irina], 1983 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - [Nagritskaita, Leta], 1981 December 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - [Naidenovich, Adel'], 1972 December 23-1979 September 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - [Naletov, Viktor], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - [Naritsa, Mikhail], 1970-1977 January 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - [Narskii, I.S.], 1970 October 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - [Nashpits, Mark], 1980 March 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Naumov, [Eduard], 1973-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - [Naumov, Vladislav], 1987 July 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - [Nazarian, Robert], 1969 September 31-1983 February 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - [Nazarov, Vasilii], 1981 August 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - [Nechaev, Vadim], 1978 April 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - [Nedgar, Georgii], 1970 December24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - [Neizvestnii, Ernst], 1975 July 25-1977 January 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - [Nekipelov, Viktor], 1974 March 5-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - [Nekipelov, Viktor], 1977-1981; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - [Nekipelov, Viktor], 1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Nekipelov, Viktor, 1972-1979; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Nekipelov, Viktor, 1978-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - [Nekrich, Aleksandr], 1976 April 19-1976 July 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - [Neplekhovich, Vladimir], 1980October 4- 1985 April 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - [Nikitenkov, Vasilii], 1971 August 25-1996 Noverm ber 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - [Nikitin, Aleksei], 1971 August 6-1981 October 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - [Nikitkov, Aleksandr], 1979 March 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - [Niklus, Mart], 1977 April 23-1989 February 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - [Nikolaev, Evgenii], 1977 November 25-1979 December 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - [Nikolaev, Viktor], 1990 May 25-1990 September 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - [Nimerenko, Vladimir], 1980 February 28-1983 March 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - [Nitsoo, Viktor], 1981 April 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - [Nosik, Boris], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - [Novak, Leonid], 1980 November 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - [Novikov, Andrei], 1988 May 26-1990; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - [Novikov, Mark], 1978 November 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - [Novodvorskaia, Valeriia], 1978 December 9-1984 June 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - [Novosel'stev, Valentin], 1981-1984 June 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - [Nudel', Ida], 1974 December 10-1982 April 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - [Obukhov, German], 1982; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - [Odintsov, Igor'], 1987 June 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 15)